感觉好像回到了我妈的子宫里
Ah, it's like I'm back in my mother's womb.
不过那里没食物这里才有
Only, there's food here.
这些电子烟真是瞎爆了
Ugh, those e-cigs are so stupid.
的确 抽真烟有害性命
I mean, smoking real cigarettes kills you,
但抽假烟会让我想要你命
but smoking fake ones makes me want to kill you.
人家不是抽烟 是吞云吐雾
They're not smoking. They're vaping.
惨了 他传给她了
Uh-oh. He just passed it to her.
有人要被约会强"烟"啦
Someone's getting date vaped.
我才刚学会怎么用新时代手机
I just figured out the new phones.
现在我还得学怎么抽烟吗
Now I've got to figure out how to smoke?
早知道所有事情得重学一遍
If I wanted to learn everything all over again,
我宁愿中风了之
I would have had a stroke.
抱歉各位 餐厅里不许这样
Hey guys, sorry, but you're not allowed to do that in here.
我说的不是你们的衣服哦
And I'm not talking about your outfits.
等我拿账单来再谈你们的衣服
I'll get to those when I bring the check.
别紧张 这又不是香烟
Relax, it's not a cigarette.
这玩意是用电池
It has a battery.
我的电动棒也是用电池 可是...
Yeah, so does my vibrator, but...
我也不能在这里用那玩意啊
can't use that in here either.
我不赞同这条规定
I didn't approve that rule.
我们的小蛋糕T恤好像订太多件了
Well, I think we ordered too many of our cupcake tees.
咱们这里没被穿过的衣服
There are more unworn shirts here
比马修·麦康纳衣柜里的还多
than in Matthew McConaughey's closet.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
快看我
Look at me.
我穿着礼拜日专用胸罩 因为我刚去了教堂
I got my Sunday bra on 'cause I just came from church.
去了我的教堂吗
Was it my church?
我和奥列格在找一个教堂办婚礼
Oleg and I are looking for one to get married in.
那教堂一定得有轮椅坡道
And it's got to have a wheelchair ramp
因为我有好多亲戚生来就没有腿骨
'cause I've got a lot of cousins who were born without leg bones.
苏菲 我真为你高兴
I'm so excited for you, Sophie.
你值得拥有世上所有的幸福
You deserve all the happiness in the world.
我也值得 但看来是没机会成真了
I mean, so do I, but that's obviously not happening.
你唧唧歪歪 可怜巴巴完了吗
Are you done with your pity-party?
因为我还有事跟麦克斯说呢
'Cause I got to speak to Max.
麦克斯 你愿意当我的伴娘吗
Max, do you want to be my maid of honor?
我宁愿被一只兔子活活啃死
I would rather be eaten alive by a rabbit.
虽然会痛很久 但好歹不会那么丢人
Which would take a long time and be a lot less embarrassing.
苏菲 你也不会想我当你伴娘的
And Sophie, you don't really want me to be your maid of honor.
是啊 我的确不想
That's right. I don't.
所以你跟我干嘛聊这事呢
So why are we even talking about it?
苏菲 虽然被你邀请我深感荣幸
Sophie, as honored as I am that you asked,
但我这人真不适合做这事 你懂吧 兄弟
it's just not really my thing, you know, man?
你真的不适合吗
Is this really not your thing?
有谁适合做这种事啊
It's nobody's thing.
大家都是因为该做 所以才做的
You just do it 'cause you're supposed to,
就像漂白自己的牙齿或菊花一样
like bleaching your teeth or your anus.
幸好伴娘没我的事
Thank God I'm off the list,
不然伴娘spa日肯定有得好受
'cause that bridesmaid spa day is gonna be rough.
对不起 是因为我五年级时
Look, I'm sorry, it's just, I was a maid of honor
当过我妈跟她邪教教头的伴娘
in fifth grade when my mom married her cult leader.
然后在一周后
And then she was my maid of honor
我嫁给教头时 她当了我伴娘
when I married him a week later.
所以我这辈子伴娘的额度算是用完了
So I'm kind of maid-of-honored out.
那我试试看找我当年姐妹会的姐妹
Maybe I'll get one of my old sorority sisters
来当我的伴娘吧
to be my bridesmaid.
我要回家去查查
I'm gonna go home and find out
她们之中还有谁瘦得能塞进普通客机
which one is still thin enough to fly commercial.
我们该把这些T恤放哪去呢
All right, where are we gonna store all these shirts?
我们这里面已经太挤了
It's already too crowded in here
充满了小蛋糕 耻辱 与失败
with all the cupcakes, shame, and failure.
其中一些可以透过小蛋糕窗口卖出去
We'll sell some of these at the cupcake window,
这里面还有20件
20 of these are already going
已经要卖给曼哈顿的精品服饰店
to that fancy boutique in Manhattan,
剩下这些 如果我们运气好
and the rest, maybe we'll get lucky
说不定有基佬少棒队伍会要呢
and find a gay little league team.
我知道了
Oh, I know!
咱们去买醉吧
Let's get drunk.
你解决任何事情的方式都是这个
That's your solution to everything.
我是说真的
Seriously.
我们带一些T恤去那家新开酒吧
We need to just take some to that new bar
里面有花20块买杯酒的傻逼
where idiots pay $20 for a drink.
又醉又蠢 就是我们的目标客户啦
Drunk and stupid, that's our target audience.
我履历表上的特殊技能 也是又醉又蠢
And also, the special skills I've listed on my resume.
你的意思是我们要没节操到
So you're saying we're gonna stoop so low
用行李袋装T恤去酒吧里卖吗
as to sell T-shirts out of a duffle bag in a bar?
好吧 我们也就那样了
Yeah, we're there.
你觉得做这个能有多少薪水啊
How much do you think this pays?
因为我也可以啊
'Cause I can do that.
你的确是可以啊
Yes, you can.
你只缺一把梯子外加一对奶子
All you need is a stepladder and boobs.
感觉像《星际迷航:下一代》主题酒吧
Feel like the: Star Trek: Next Generation bar.
注意有没有戴着奇形怪帽的琥碧·戈柏出没
Keep your eyes peeled for Whoopi Goldberg in a crazy hat.
真不敢相信我正在未来
I can't believe I'm selling T-shirts
从旅行袋里拿出T恤来卖
out of a duffle bag in the future, too.
我完全支持工作与享乐并行
Yeah. I fully support mixing business and pleasure.
我做爱最爽的一次是跟我打工面包店的老板
Best sex I ever had was with my boss at a Panera Bread.
我记得你说你最爽的一次
I thought you said the best sex you ever had
是跟一个"六指淫魔"啊
was with a dude with six fingers.
同一个人啊
Same guy.
他做三明治[让人高潮]的速度可快了
Man, could he make a sandwich crazy fast.
想给女朋友买件酷T恤吗
Hi. Want to buy a cool tee for your girlfriend?
我问问我女朋友想不想要
Let me see if my girlfriend wants a tee.
你想要T恤吗 亲爱的
You want a tee, honey?
等等 别走
Hey! Hey!
兄台留步
Not so fast.
衣服后面写了"奶油[精液]满满"呢
They say "Cream filled" On the back.
怎么样 觉得如何
Huh, boys? Anything?
未来的男同们真没劲
Wow, gays aren't fun in the future.
而耶稣在未来又满血复活了
Jesus comes back in the future.
包袱里装的是什么呀
So what's in the bag?
我从来没在酒吧里见过真有"包袱"的女孩
I've never met a girl at a bar with actual baggage.
真有意思 是情感"包袱"的哏吧
That's funny because you mean like emotional.
你真是美呆了
You're really beautiful.
圣经里你没这么帅啊
You weren't nearly this hot in the book.
我能请两位女士喝杯酒吗
So can I get you ladies a drink?
当然 你直接把这水变成酒就好啦
Sure, you could jut change this water into wine.
你能为我像这样甩头吗 一次就好
Can you, like, do this for me, just, like, once?
上酒 我请
Drinks on me.
"上"酒 酒真幸运
Oh, lucky them.
我有好几个月
I haven't heard I'm beautiful
没从非流浪汉口中听到你好美了
from a non-homeless person in months.
看他发型 是不是流浪汉还说不准哦
Well, with that hair, the jury's still out.
我能吻你吗
Hey, can I kiss you?
小亲一口应该没...
I suppose a peck wouldn't--
神马
Say what?
-在下詹姆士 -在下湿哒哒
- I'm James. - I'm wet.
我是指手臂压到吧台上的水了
Because my arm was sitting in water on the bar.
麦克斯 刚才太火辣了
That was so hot, Max.
我有如野兽般被他吸引住了
I have, like, this animal attraction to him.
什么野兽 发浪单身宅狗吗
What animal? The Horny Nerd?
这样吧 我先撤 你留下慢慢搞
Look, I'll leave. You stay and do your thing.
-但我们一起来[高潮]的 -我知道你俩是这样
- But we came together. - Yeah, I know you guys did.
他亲你的那一瞬间就"发生"了
It happened, like, the second he kissed you.
我不是这种人 我才刚认识他
I don't do this. I just met him.
卡洛琳
Look, Caroline.
我没读过圣经
I haven't read the Bible.
但我知道当耶稣再来之时
But I know that when Jesus returns,
你必追随他回到他的公寓
you must follow him back to his apartment.
放开自我
Let go...
让主耶稣
let God...
到达"三垒"
get to third base.
麦克斯 卡洛琳呢
Max, where's Caroline?
我一整天都没看到她
I haven't seen her all day.
但我猜她是"上天堂"了
But I'm guessing she's in heaven.
我来了 我来了
I'm here, I'm here.
不 她是在地狱
Nope, she's in hell.
炮后羞耻步 踽踽独行之
Walk of shame, party of one.
老妹
Girl.
老 妹
Gir-irl!
告诉我发生的一切事情
Tell me everything that happened.
所有细节全不许放过
Leave out no details.
太疯狂了 实在太火辣
It was insane. I mean, like, so hot.
像加勒比海 或我们共浴那次这么火辣
Like the Caribbean or our shower that one time.
你们俩在庆祝个什么劲
What are you two celebrating?
反正我知道不是因为活干得好
I know it isn't a job well done.
我们在庆祝《星球大战第七部》
We are celebrating the release of the new:
网上放出新预告片了
Star Wars: Episode VII trailer online.
真的咩
Seriously?
麦克斯 能做的我们全做了
Max, we did everything.
我们...
We--
奥列格 能给我们一点私人空间吗
Oleg, can you give us some privacy?
干嘛啊
What?
不准我待女厕里
I can't be in the ladies' room.
厨房也不让待啊
I can't be in the kitchen.
那你们...
So did you...
没
No.
那你们...
Well, did you...
才没有
No!
那你们至少...
Well, did you at least...
天啊 怎么可能
Oh, God, no!
那你们都干啥了
Well, what did you do?
一起给植物浇水吗
Water a plant together?
我们滚床单了
We had sex.
昨晚跟今天都滚了
Last night and today.
这对我来说是大事呢
That's a big thing for me.
而且他的"事"的确很大
And, yes, it was.
是啊 在酒吧时就很明显了
Yes. That was obvious in the bar.
紧身牛仔裤基本就是"鸟巢"透视仪
Skinny jeans are just boner X-rays.
惨了 惨了
Oh, no. Oh, no.
怎么 沙拉里又进耗子了吗
What, rat in the slaw again?
我的戒指
My rings.
我忘在他家了
I left them at his place.
我得去拿回来
I have to get them back.
它们是我的一半家当呢
They're half my belongings.
就给他发短信说"我戒指忘你家了
So just text him and say, "Yo, I left my rings,
好一只大雕 加100分的颜文字" 发送
nice wiener," "100" Emoji, send.
麦克斯 我怎么可以先给男人发短信呢
Max, I can't text a guy first.
我用团购劵买性爱润滑油已经够惨了好吗
It's bad enough I have a Groupon for intimacy oil.
听我说 最惨的情况
Look, worst-case scenario,
是麦当劳去骨猪排三明治永远停卖
the McRib is gone for good.
而第二惨的情况下
Second worst-case scenario,
我们永远都可以执行两周之规
we can always implement the two-week rule.
什么两周之规
The two-week rule?
等等 是不是你得在两周内吃完泰式炒面
Wait, isn't that how long you have to eat Pad Thai
不然它会变成太屎炒面
before it becomes bad Thai?
不是 你真得好好读我的书了
No, you really have to read my book.
是指 如果他两周内不给你发短信
It means if he doesn't text for two weeks,
你就可以闯进他家拿回东西
you can break in and get your stuff.
上过那么多洋气的学校 结果你屁都没学到
All that fancy school and you didn't learn nothing.
两周了 啥都没有
Two weeks and nothing.
我真以为他会发短信呢
I really thought he'd text.
我也以为《长大成人2》会得奥斯卡奖
I also thought: Grown Ups 2 should have won the Oscar.
宝刀未老
Still got it.
加油
Come on.
稍等 在我失去我剩下的那点自尊心前...
Wait, before I lose the rest of my self-esteem...
这话你跟你正骑着的墙说吧
Tell that to the wall you're currently straddling.
让我最后再看一次我手机看他发短...
Let me just check my phone one more time to see if he--
没发
Nope.
自尊心丧失
Self-esteem gone.
我不敢跳
I'm afraid to jump.
跳 婊子 快跳
Jump, whore, jump!
我说话好像我妈教我游泳时那样
I sound like my mom teaching me how to swim.
我做到了 我做到了
I did it. I did it.
拜托 这大概就60公分高
That was, like, two feet.
我吸过比这高度还长的白粉
I've snorted lines longer.
好啦
All right.
一个平凡的周二
Just another Tuesday.
在耶稣的后院搞《珠光宝气》那套
Going all: Bling Ring in Jesus' backyard.
这里 这是他的卧房窗户
There. That's his bedroom window.
我知道是因为我有点"大声" 所以得关上窗
I know 'cause we had to close it, since I'm kind of loud.
那你做爱时也这么大声吵杂吗
Oh, what are you like during sex?
万一他在家 我该怎么做
What do I do if he's home?
你想我手起刀落秒杀他
Do you want me to kill him fast,
还是你想他被折磨至死
or do you want him to suffer?
而所谓的折磨 是看你要不要我抓住他
And by that, I mean, do you want me to hold him
让你慢慢问他为什么没打给你
while you ask him why he didn't call?
他不在家
He's not home.
根据他的照片分享网 他在快餐店里
According to this Instagram, he's at Chipotle
跟一个肩膀上有鹦鹉的人聊天呢
talking to a guy with a parrot on his shoulder.
有这时间却没空给我发条短信
He had no time to pop off a text to me.
窗卡住了 这缝隙我的巨乳过不去啊
Oh, it's stuck and I can't fit my boobs through there.
荷兰隧道我都快塞不进了 何况这里
I can barely fit them through the Holland Tunnel.
好吧 我来进
Fine. I'm going in.
贫乳妹的好处终于出现了
Finally, having no boobs pays off.
把我的腿抬起来
Lift my legs up.
行啊 可是腿在空中
Okay, but your legs in the air
不就是害你沦落至此的原因吗
kind of got you here to begin with.
-糟糕 -怎么了
- Uh-oh. - What oh?
我印象中他的被子不是花卉图案
I don't remember him having a floral duvet.
也没有床边厕所
Or a bedside toilet.
更没有狗 快拉我出来 快拉我出来
Or a dog. Pull me out! Pull me out!
你真应该看看我的书
You've got to read my book.
我有一整章是教你怎么"拔出来"
I have a whole chapter on pulling out.
不不不 不要舔我
No, no, no, no, no! Oh, stop licking me.
巴斯特 巴斯特
Buster? Buster?
有人来了
Someone's coming.
有人"来"了 你还被舔得很爽
Someone's coming, you're getting licked?
或许你来对地方了
Maybe you are in the right apartment.
快滚出我的房子 快滚出我的房子
Get out of my house! Get out of my house!
不不 这是一个天大的误会
No, no. This is a big mistake.
本 快打电话报警
Ben, call the cops!
又有瘾君子闯进咱们家了
We got another crack addict here!
我们家没有毒品
We don't have crack here!
拜托转告你的毒友们
And tell your friends!
如果我的指纹跟07年快餐店入室盗窃案吻合
If these match the prints found at an Arby's break-in in '07,
那一定是纯属巧合
it's purely coincidental.
真不敢相信我会碰上这种事
I can't believe this is happening to me.
我的人生算是完了
My life is over.
看镜头
Look at the camera.
真是太丢脸了
I'm so humiliated.
侧面照
And turn to the side.
女士 这不是在拍《服饰与美容:监狱特辑》
Ma'am, this isn't "Vogue: Behind Bars."
抱歉 警官 她是第一次
Sorry, Officer, she's a virgin.
至于我嘛
Me, myself,
曾在普罗维登斯的未成年看守所蹲过些时日
spent some time in the juvie system up in Providence.
你认识一个叫雪莉的家庭法院法官吗
You know a family court judge named Shelly?
不认识
No.
过去
Go.
警官 先等等
Officer, hold.
谢谢 但全面体腔检查时麻烦离我远点
Thanks, but stay away during the full-body cavity search.
可以拍了
Proceed.
还用你批准吗
You think?
所以你们俩小妞闯进一个老太婆的家里
So you girls broke into an old lady's house,
半个身子卡在窗台
got halfway through the window,
什么也没偷
and stole absolutely nothing.
真庆幸我为本市逮捕了你们两名大恶人
Glad I am protecting the city from you.
ISIS跟你们比算老几啊
I mean, ISIS who, right?
好了 我们走吧
All right. Let's go.
如果他有发短信给我 这一切都不会发生
If he had just texted me, none of this would be happening.
我就不会进监狱 我会在家
I wouldn't be in prison, I'd be home.
我另外一间监狱
My other prison.
慢着 如果谁有发短信给你
Uh, wait, if who had texted you?
谢谢你这么问
Thanks for asking.
我跟一个男的睡了 结果过了两周
This guy I slept with didn't text me
他都没有发短信给我
for two weeks after we had sex,
而我当时把戒指落在他家了 所以...
and I left my rings at his place, so I--
你是在执行两周之规吗
You did the two-week rule?
是的
Yeah.
但她记错地方了 因为我了解她
But she got the wrong apartment because, knowing her,
她做爱时全程都是闭着眼的
her eyes were closed the whole time.
你们怎么不早说呢
Well, why didn't you say so?
她们是执行两周之规的
We got a two-week rule over here!
来这边待着
Stay right over here.
很快就放你们走了
We'll get you out soon.
我的警棍落在警监家了
I left my billy club at the Captain's house.
他还有三天时间
He's got three more days.
瞧 你看见啦
See? See?
肯定会没事的
It's gonna be fine.
我们只需待上一小时就可以走啦
We'll just chill here for an hour.
就像在更犀利的亮视点店配眼镜
It's like an edgier Lens Crafters.
我该怎么跟我爸爸说
What am I gonna tell my father?
打一通监狱内线电话吗
A prisoned prison call?
我不能蹲监狱
I can't be here.
I can't be here!
不不 快回来 我们本来没事的
No! No! Come back! We were good!
蠢妞
Dumb move.
比我和警监睡还蠢
Dumber than me and the Captain.
我猜我们的眼镜一个小时内是不会好了
Let me guess, our glasses won't be ready in an hour.
说出来都没人信 你居然害我们在监狱里被捕了
I can't believe you got us arrested in jail.
此路通向何方
Where are we going?
虽然我的人生已经"此路不通"了
I mean, besides nowhere in life.
你们白白浪费了你们的免费出狱卡
You girls lost your get-out-of-jail-free card.
现在你们得找人花钱保你们出去了
You're gonna have to get someone to bail you out.
所以先进拘留室待着吧
You're going in the holding cell.
喂 鲜肉到
Yo! Fresh meat!
抱歉 我得维护我煞气的名声
Sorry, I have a reputation to uphold.
麦克斯 我好害怕呀
Max, I'm scared.
交给我吧
I got this.
各位 她已经是我的妞了
Yo! She's already my bitch!
所以你们别想打她主意 抱歉啦
So she can't be anyone else's. Sorry.
拉住我的皮带
Hold my belt.
-什么 -听话
- What? - Do it!
你好 你好
'Sup, 'sup?
很好 很好
Cool, cool.
50个女人就1个厕所
50 women, 1 toilet?
感觉就像"观点"节目组的后台
It's like backstage at:The View.
麦克斯 我做不来
Max, I can't handle this.
我真的做不来
I can't handle this.
我连《绿里奇迹》都不敢看
I couldn't even watch:The Green Mile.
放松 这里跟玩似的
Relax. This is play-jail.
我们不是真的在坐牢
It's not like we're doing real time.
快换上你的霸气表情
Just put on your game face.
我没有什么霸气[游戏]表情
I don't have a game face.
除非这场游戏是"我放弃 我的人生完蛋了"
Unless the game is "I Give Up, My Life Is Over,"
那这表情就行了
then this will do.
你最好做点什么
Well, do something,
因为这表情马上就会被吓得无影踪
because that's about to get wiped off your face
因为一个满是纹身的女汉子
by the bruiser covered in tattoos
正朝我们走来呢
making her way to us right now.
你们俩要报名参加才艺表演吗
You guys signing up for the talent show?
我没听错吧
Excuse me?
没 因为监狱人满为患 我们有些人
Yeah. Some of us have been in here for days,
已经在这里待了好几天了
due to prison overcrowding.
所以守卫让我们自娱自乐
So the guards let us put on a show.
只要不玩出人命就行
As long as nobody dies.
哇 监狱变好多哦
Wow, prison has changed.
或许我对监狱的看法过于理想化了
Maybe I have a Norman Rockwell idea of prison,
但排队打饭的时用刀捅告密者的文化去哪了
but, uh, what happened to shanking a snitch in the food line?
才艺表演 这一点也不吓人
Oh, a talent show, that's not scary at all.
我曾是我的游艇俱乐部才艺表演的冠军
You know, I won my yacht club talent show
连续三年 10到13岁那组的冠军一直是我
three years in a row, in the 10 to 13 division.
真是太巧了
That's crazy!
我因为重汽车窃盗罪也得蹲个10到13年呢
I'm looking at 10 to 13 for grand theft auto.
我真失礼
Where are my manners?
我是塔娜雅
I'm Tanaya.
我是麦克斯 她是卡洛琳
I'm Max. This is Caroline.
但你可以叫我们的帮派名
But you can call us by our gang names,
白闪电和黑刀侠
White Lightning and The Blade.
苏菲 我需要你保释我和卡洛琳出狱
Sophie, I need you to bail me and Caroline out jail.
我们被控告非法闯入他人住宅
We got charged with breaking and entering,
卡洛琳也让一个男人对她"做"了同样的事
which is also what Caroline let a guy do to her,
所以我们才进了监狱
and that's why we're here.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, jeez, Max.
这通电话真让我左右为难
I mean, that's a tough call.
人家不知道能不能去啦
I mean, I don't know if I can.
但我这人真不适合做这事
Yeah, it's really not my thing.
你懂吧 兄弟
You know, man?
我懂 我活该
I get it. I deserved that.
我拒绝了你 所以你现在也拒绝我
I said no to you, so you're saying no to me.
正所谓古语有云 "以两牙还一牙"
Like the old saying, "Tit for bigger tat."
是呀
Yeah. Hmm.
好吧 我想想
All right, let's see.
如果是我的伴娘进监狱 我会去保她出来
Uh, I would bail my maid of honor out of jail.
好吧 好吧
Fine. Fine.
我会当你的伴娘
I'll be your maid of honor.
我会给你买鸡鸡吸管
I'll buy you penis straws,
还有那种鼻子那里是鸡鸡的眼镜
and those glasses where the nose is a penis.
太好了 那鸡鸡形状的意面呢
Yeah! And the penis-shaped pasta?
我都买给你
I'll do it all.
我在牢里不会有事
I can handle the slammer,
但卡洛琳可没生还的机会
but Caroline doesn't stand a chance.
我看见一个女人看她的眼神
I saw a woman looking at her
就像在看一块卡通里的猪排
like she was a cartoon pork chop.
好的 晚点见啦
Okay. Well, I'll see you soon.
小心背后哦
And watch your back.
对了
Oh, you know what?
你在女子监狱 所以是...
It's a ladies' prison, so...
小心前面
watch your front.
这是你的牌吗
Is this your card?
不是
No.
是
Yes!
是 就是我那张牌
Yes, that's my card.
太神奇了
Amazing.
我有错过什么吗
Okay. What'd I miss?
魔术表演和即兴表演
The magic show and the improv troupe.
她们让观众说一个词
They asked the audience for a word.
我说了"救命"
I said, "Help."
苏菲晚点会拿钱来交保释金
Sophie's coming down with bail money,
不过要先等她的火鸡出炉
as soon as her turkey is out of the oven.
估计得4到4个半小时吧 得看她填的什么馅
So 4, 4 1/2 hours, depending on the stuffing.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
等等 她是来保咱俩出去的 对吧
Wait. Bail for both of us, right?
她一开始不愿意保两个
That wasn't her original offer.
但经过一番磋商后 她同意了
But after some negotiating, we got there.
那你得做什么才能...
What did you have to do to--
麦克斯 你不会是同意...
Max, you didn't agree to--
是的
Yup.
想象我穿着一条低胸桃红色的裙子
Picture me in something low-cut and peach.
淫荡小桃红哦
A slutty peach.
你是为了我这么做吗
You'd do that for me?
我真是既感动又震惊啊
I'm touched and shocked.
我以为你早就忘了我 跟门卫打了一炮
I thought you'd have forgotten me, had sex with the door guard,
然后现在已经到停车场了
and been halfway across the parking lot by now.
可惜啊 门卫不喜欢我
Yeah, well, he wasn't into me, so...
出狱羞耻步 齐头并进之
Walk of shame, party of two.
姑娘们 听说你们进了监狱
Girls, I heard you got locked up.
是啊 我们得做30小时的社区服务
Yup. We have to do 30 hours of community service.
卡洛琳还在才艺表演上赢了独自享用
And Caroline won six minutes of privacy on the toilet
6分钟厕所的时间
in the talent show.
也没那么独自啦
Well, not so private.
一个穿着工作靴的女人在我嘘嘘的时候
I had to tinkle while a woman in work boots
跟我狠狠四目相交了一番
made heavy eye-contact.
我也曾进过监狱一次
I went to prison once for
因为在错误的时间 出现在错误的地点
being at the wrong place at the wrong time.
也就是说 我当时去了南方
Meaning, I was down south.
瞧瞧谁从大牢回来了
Look who's back from the big house.
阿憨 对你来说所有房子都是"大"房子
Every house is a big house for you, Han.
小心行事 前科犯
Watch your step, ex-con,
否则我会让警察叔叔再把你关进去
or I'll get them to haul you back in
因为你冒充服务员
for impersonating a waitress.
真不敢相信我会这么说 但我蛮想念这个地方
I can't believe I'm saying this, but I missed this place.
当我下了号子里 跟我的姐妹塔娜雅一起蹲时
When I was up in the pen, doing time with my girl, Tanaya--
真当自己是女子监狱一霸啦
Well, orange you the new black?
你们俩在女子监狱待得爽吗
So did you two have fun in ladies' prison?
告诉我 里面是不是一切都跟我收藏的17部
And tell me, is it anything like the 17 XXX movies
女子监狱主题A片一样呢
I have with that title?
好吧 我失去了两个最漂亮的戒指
Okay, so I lost two of my best rings.
也就是损失了11块
So I'm out $11.
我意识到自己比想象中坚强
I realized I'm tougher than I thought.
我在监狱里过唱歌 我玩过一夜情
I sang in prison. I had a one-night stand.
我跟约翰尼·卡什[有钱]没差别嘛
I'm practically Johnny Cash.
错 你是约翰尼·没钱
Well, Johnny No Cash.